Register of the Library of Social History Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Fourth International Series, 1894-1991 (Box 1-199)
  - Indonesia
    - Central Committee of Indonesian Independence, Australia. Pamphlet. Republic of Indonesia, (1946) (Box-folder 105: 5)
    - Communist Party
      - Indonesian Tribune. No. 1, (1966) (Box-folder 105: 6)
      - Pamphlet. D. N. Aidit, Dare, Dare, and Dare Again!, (1963) (Box-folder 105: 7)
      - Printed article, 1965 (Box-folder 105: 8)
    - Indonesia League of America. Leaflets, 1945 (Box-folder 105: 9)
    - Indonesian Committee for a Free Indonesia of San Francisco. Pamphlet. Si Barani and Soekma Ngembara, Why the Indonesians Revolt, (1945) (Box-folder 105: 10)
    - Indonesian Independence Committee. Pamphlet. Dutch Imperialism Exposed, (ca. 1946) (Box-folder 105: 11)
    - Partai Murba. Pamphlet. Perdjandjian San Francisco membahajakan politik bebas, (1951) (Box-folder 105: 12)
    - Unclassified by organization. T. Soedarso, "Indonesia: PKI and Trotskyist" (typescript) (Box-folder 105: 13)
  - Iran
    - Committee for Women's Democratic Rights in Iran. Women and Struggle in Iran. No. 4, (1985) (Box-folder 105: 14)
    - Organization of Iranian People's Fedaiian
      - International Fedaii. Vol. 3 no. 3, (1986) (Box-folder 105: 15)
      - Pamphlets. A Look at Three Years of Revolutionary Experience of the Masses; An Open Letter to the People's Mojahedin Organization of Iran; Against Liquidationism in Defence of Principled Unity; Iranian Revolution and the Duties of the Proletariat, (1981) (1981) (1982) (1982) (Box-folder 105: 16)
    - Unclassified by organization
      - [ Socialist Review]. No. 1, (1978) (Box-folder 105: 17)
      - Pamphlets. Ernest Mandel, [ What Is Trotskyism?]; [ Dialectics of World Revolution]; Ernest Mandel, [ On Bureaucracy]; Leon Trotsky, [ Results and Prospects]; Ernest Mandel, [ Peaceful Coexistence and World Revolution]; [ The Arab Revolution], (1972) (1974) (1976) (1976) (1977) (n.d.) (Box-folder 105: 18)
  - Iraq
    - Iraqi Democratic Union in U.S. and Canada
      - Iraqi Democratic Voice. N.n., (1990) (Box-folder 105: 19)
      - Sawt al-itihad. N.n., (1988) (Box-folder 105: 20)
    - National, Democratic and Patriotic Front in Iraq. The Front. No. 2, (1983) (Box-folder 105: 21)
    - Unclassified by organization. Mohamad Yonis, "Another Coup d'Etat in Iraq?" (typescript), 1965 (Box-folder 105: 22)
  - Ireland (Box 106)
    - Communist Party. Pamphlet. For People's Unity, (1979) (Box-folder 106: 1)
    - Independent Socialist Party
      - The Irish Left. No. 1, (1977) (Box-folder 106: 2)
      - Pamphlet. The Independent Socialist Party: An Introduction, (1977) (Box-folder 106: 3)
      - Leaflet, 1978 (Box-folder 106: 4)
    - Irish Marxist Society. Newsletter. N.n., (1977) (Box-folder 106: 5)
    - Irish Republican Socialist Party. Leaflets, 1977 (Box-folder 106: 6)
    - Irish Workers Group
      - An Solas. No. 12, 14-15/16, (1966) (Box-folder 106: 7)
      - Discussion. No. 1-4, (1967) (Box-folder 106: 8)
      - Irish Militant. Vol. 1 no. 5, 8-9, vol. 2 no. 1-12, vol. 3 no. 1, 3-5, 7, (1966) (1967) (1968) (Box-folder 106: 9)
    - Irish Young Socialists. Youth Bulletin. No. 2, no. 25, (1970) (1972) (Box-folder 106: 10)
    - League for a Workers' Republic
      - Revolutionary International. No. 1, (1974) (Box-folder 106: 11)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 106: 12)
      - Leaflets, 1969 (Box-folder 106: 13)
    - Movement for a Socialist Republic
      - Internal Discussion Bulletin. N.n., n.n., (1977) (1978) (Box-folder 106: 14)
      - Workers' Fight. No. 1, 3-5, no. 6, n.n., (1976) (1977) (Box-folder 106: 15)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 106: 16)
      - Pamphlet. O'Connor Lysaght, End of a Liberal: The Literary Politics of Conor Cruise O'Brien, (1976) (Box-folder 106: 17)
      - Leaflets, 1972 (Box-folder 106: 18)
    - People's Democracy
      - Free Citizen. No. 10, (n.d.) (Box-folder 106: 19)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 106: 20)
      - Pamphlets. Ernest Mandel, What Is Trotskyism?; Prisoners of Partition: H-Block / Armagh, (1979) (1979) (Box-folder 106: 21)
      - Leaflets, 1973 (Box-folder 106: 22)
    - Republican Socialist Tendency. Leaflet (Box-folder 106: 23)
    - Revolutionary Marxist Group
      - Internal Bulletin. No. 1-3, n.d. (1973) (Box-folder 106: 24)
      - International Bulletin of Celtic History and Sociology. Vol. 1 no. 1, 3-6, vol. 2 no. 1, 3, (1973) (1974) (Box-folder 106: 25)
      - Irish Trotskyist. No. 1-3, no. 4-13, (1972) (1973) (Box-folder 106: 26)
      - Marxist Review. No. 1, no. 2-5, no. 6, (1972) (1973) (1974) (Box-folder 107: 1)
      - The Torch. No. 1, (1972) (Box-folder 107: 2)
      - The Worker. N.n., (1972) (Box-folder 107: 3)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 107: 4)
      - Pamphlets. British Strategy in Northern Ireland; The E.E.C. and Ireland, (1975) (n.d.) (Box-folder 107: 5)
      - Leaflets, 1975 (Box-folder 107: 6)
    - Revolutionary Socialist Party
      - Workers' Republic. No. 1, (1947) (Box-folder 107: 7)
      - Internal circulated document, 1948 (Box-folder 107: 8)
      - Leaflets, 1945 (Box-folder 107: 9)
    - Sinn Féin
      - Teoiric. No. 3, (ca. 1973) (Box-folder 107: 10)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 107: 11)
      - Pamphlets. The I.R.A. in the 70's; J. De Courcy Ireland, Revolutionary Movements of the Past (1971); ï¿½ire Nua; Ireland: The Facts / ï¿½ire: Na Fiorais, (1970) (1971) (1971) (Box-folder 107: 12)
      - Leaflets, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 107: 13)
    - Socialist Labour Party
      - Internal Bulletin. No. 4, (1978) (Box-folder 107: 14)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1977 (Box-folder 107: 15)
    - Socialist Workers' Movement. Internal Bulletin. No. 3, (1972) (Box-folder 107: 16)
    - Students for Democratic Action
      - Confrontation. N.n., (ca. 1969) (Box-folder 107: 17)
      - SDA Newsletter. No. 1-3, (1970) (Box-folder 107: 18)
    - Workers League
      - Marxist Journal. Vol. 2 no. 1, (1976) (Box-folder 107: 19)
      - Leaflet, 1974 (Box-folder 107: 20)
    - Young Socialists
      - The Plough. N.n., (1971) (Box-folder 107: 21)
      - Young Socialist. No. 7, no. 14, n.n., n.n., (1969) (1970) (1971) (n.d.) (Box-folder 107: 22)
    - Unclassified by organization
      - Comhar. Vol. 30 no. 9, (1971) (Box-folder 107: 23)
      - Socialist Appeal. No. 1, (1939) (Box-folder 107: 24)
      - Pamphlets. James Larkin, Larkin's Scathing Indictment of the Dublin Capitalists; Fianna Fail: The I.R.A. Connection, (1913) (ca. 1971) (Box-folder 107: 25)
      - Leaflets, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 107: 26)
  - Israel (Box 108)
    - Israeli Revolutionary Action Committee. Israc. No. 2, (1970) (Box-folder 108: 1)
    - Israeli Socialist Organization
      - Matzpen. No. 75, (1974) (Box-folder 108: 2)
      - [ Mole]. No. 10, (1972) (Box-folder 108: 3)
      - Internal circulated document, 1966 (Box-folder 108: 4)
      - English translations of journal articles, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 108: 5)
      - Pamphlets. The Other Israel; [ Strike Strategy]; [ Who We Are]; [ Everything You Wanted to Know about Socialism], (1968) (1971) (1972) (1973) (Box-folder 108: 6)
      - Leaflets, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 108: 7)
    - Revolutionary Communist Alliance. English translation of internal circulated document, 1970 (Box-folder 108: 8)
    - Revolutionary Communist League
      - La brèche. No. 1, (1975) (Box-folder 108: 9)
      - Rojo. N.n., no. 2-3, (1975) (1977) (Box-folder 108: 10)
      - Pamphlets. Socialisme ou Massada?; [ The 1977 Elections: Against the Zionist Parties], (1975) (1977) (Box-folder 108: 11)
      - Leaflets, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 108: 12)
    - Workers League
      - [ Avant-Garde]. No. 28, no. 29, (1976) (1978) (Box-folder 108: 13)
      - Pamphlets. La voie de la révolution socialiste en Palestine; Hebrew version of same, (1978) (Box-folder 108: 14)
    - Unclassified by organization
      - [ Voice of the Worker]. No. 36-41, (1977) (Box-folder 108: 15)
      - [ Way of the Spark]. N.n., no. 6, (1977) (1978) (Box-folder 108: 16)
      - Pamphlet. Israel and the Arabs (issued by the Socialist Workers Party [U.S.], 1969) (Box-folder 108: 17)
      - Leaflets and clipping, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 108: 18)
  - Italy
    - Avanguardia Operaia. Pamphlet. La concezione del partito in Lenin: dai gruppi al partito, (1970) (Box-folder 108: 19)
    - Centro di Vigilanza Rivoluzionaria. Leaflet, 1973 (Box-folder 108: 20)
    - Centro Provvisorio Nazionale per la Costruzione del Partito Comunista Internazionalista (IV Internazionale). Leaflets, 1943 (Box-folder 108: 21)
    - Circolo Giaime Pintor. Leaflet, 1966 (Box-folder 108: 22)
    - Circolo Talpa Rossa. Talpa rossa. No. 1, n.n., 4, no. 7-8, (1972) (1973) (Box-folder 108: 23)
    - Collettivo Punto Rosso
      - Punto rosso. N.n., no. 4, n.n., no. 7, (1975) (Box-folder 108: 24)
      - Rivoluzione permanente. No. 1, (1973) (Box-folder 108: 25)
    - Collettivo Studenti Rivoluzionari. Bollettino. No. 2, (1972) (Box-folder 108: 26)
    - Federazione dei Comunisti Marxisti-Leninisti. Pamphlet. Tesi del 1o Congresso, (1967) (Box-folder 108: 27)
    - Frazione Marxista Rivoluzionaria (Box 109)
      - Bollettino
        - No. 1-4, 6, (1975) (Box-folder 109: 1)
        - No. 1 [sic], 8-14, (1976) (Box-folder 109: 2)
        - No. 15-16, (1977) (Box-folder 109: 3)
      - En route. No. 1-2, (1978) (Box-folder 109: 4)
      - Leaflet, 1976 (Box-folder 109: 5)
    - Gruppi Comunisti Rivoluzionari
      - Bandiera rossa. No. 11 supp., (1973) (Box-folder 109: 6)
      - Bollettino interno
        - N.n., (1970) (Box-folder 109: 7)
        - No. 1-11., (1971) (Box-folder 109: 8)
          Includes English translation of no. 5
        - No. 1 supp., (1972) (Box-folder 109: 9)
        - No. 1-3, 5-7, n.n. (World Congress preparatory series, 1973) (Box-folder 109: 10)
        - No. 1-14 (National Conference preparatory series, 1973) (Box-folder 109: 11)
        - No. 15, 17-19, 22 (National Conference preparatory series, 1973) (Box-folder 109: 12)
        - No. 5-6, 9-11, 42, (1975) (Box-folder 110: 1)
        - N.n., (1977) (Box-folder 110: 2)
        - N.n., (1978) (Box-folder 110: 3)
        - No. 1., (n.d.) (Box-folder 110: 4)
      - Bollettino universitario. N.n., (1973) (Box-folder 110: 5)
      - Rivoluzione permanente. No. 2, n.n., n.n., (1971) (1972) (1973) (Box-folder 110: 6)
      - La scintilla. No. 1, n.n., (1973) (Box-folder 110: 7)
      - Soviet. No. 1-2, (1973) (Box-folder 110: 8)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 110: 9)
      - Pamphlets
        - Livio Maitan, Crisi della borghesia e lotta rivoluzionaria del proletariato; Livio Maitan, I marxisti rivoluzionari e le tesi degli 81; Programma transitorio e rivoluzione socialista; VII congresso mondiale e congresso di riunificazione della IV Internazionale: documento e relazioni, (1953) (1961) (1962) (1964) (Box-folder 110: 10)
        - Livio Maitan, Dai processi di Mosca alla caduta di Krusciov, (1965) (Box-folder 110: 11)
        - Contro l'aumento dei prezzi in difesa del salario; Ligue communiste; La tragica lezione del Cile; Compromesso storico o governo operaio?; Lotta di classe nell'ex colonia italiana; Livio Maitan, La crisi economica e la risposta dei rivoluzionari; Statuti dei Gruppi comunisti rivoluzionari e della Quarta internazionale, (1973) (1973) (1973) (1974) (1974) (1974) (1974) (Box-folder 110: 12)
        - 20 risposte sul Portogallo oggi; Violenza necessaria, inutile e dannosa; Documenti per il congresso nazionale; Edgardo Pellegrini, Che politica verso il PCI?; Contro l'unitá nazionale, per l'unitá del proletariato!; Aborto libero gratuito e assistito; Perché votare, per chi votare, (1975) (1975) (1976) (1977) (1978) (n.d.) (n.d.) (Box-folder 110: 13)
      - Leaflets (Box 111)
        - 1964-1971 (Box-folder 111: 1)
        - 1972 (Box-folder 111: 2)
        - 1973 (Box-folder 111: 3)
        - 1976-1977 (Box-folder 111: 4)
        - Undated (Box-folder 111: 5)
    - Gruppo Rivoluzione Permanente. Rivoluzione permanente. N.n., no. 4, n.n., (1974) (1975) (Box-folder 111: 6)
    - Lega Comunista Rivoluzionaria
      - Misma lucha / Stessa lotta. N.n., n.n., (1979) (1980) (Box-folder 111: 7)
      - Rivoluzione. N.n., (1982) (Box-folder 111: 8)
    - Lega Operaia Rivoluzionaria. Politica operaia. N.n., (1984) (Box-folder 111: 9)
    - Lega Socialista Rivoluzionaria
      - Avanzata proletaria. No. 8, (1982) (Box-folder 111: 10)
      - Bollettino. No. 1, n.n., (1982) (Box-folder 111: 11)
      - Internal circulated document, 1982 (Box-folder 111: 12)
    - Movimento Università Negativa. Pamphlet. Manifesto per una università negativa, (1967) (Box-folder 111: 13)
    - Partito Nazionale Fascista. Pamphlet. Fascism and the Working Classes, (1936) (Box-folder 111: 14)
    - Partito Operaio Comunista (Bolscevico-Leninista)
      - Bollettino. No. 4/5., (1945) (Box-folder 111: 15)
      - Bollettino interno. No. 1-6, (1947) (Box-folder 111: 16)
      - L'internazionale. Vol. 2 no. 3, (1945) (Box-folder 111: 17)
      - IV internazionale. Vol. 2 no. 3, 5-7, 9-10, vol. 3 no. 2, 4-7, (1946) (1947) (Box-folder 111: 18)
      - Internal circulated document, 1946 (Box-folder 111: 19)
      - Leaflets,., 1945 (Box-folder 111: 20)
    - Studenti Comunisti Rivoluzionari
      - Soviet. No. 1, (n.d.) (Box-folder 111: 21)
      - Leaflet, 1973 (Box-folder 111: 22)
    - Tendenza Marxista Rivoluzionaria. Internal circulated document, 1975 (Box-folder 111: 23)
    - Unclassified by organization
      - Avanguardia comunista. No. 19-20, no. 21/22-25, 27, (1974) (1975) (Box-folder 111: 24)
      - Contro informazione. Vol. 2 no. 1, (n.d.) (Box-folder 111: 25)
      - Falcemartello. No. 8, no. 1, (1967) (1975) (Box-folder 111: 26)
      - Soviet. No. 1, no. 1-4, (1971) (1972) (Box-folder 112: 1)
      - Pamphlets. Angelica Balabanoff, Il traditore / The Traitor; Savino Russo, Il delitto Matteotti; Livio Maitan, Trotskij storico della rivoluzione russa; Pierre Frank, Riformisti e rivoluzionari nel maggio francese; Clara Zetkin, Lenin; Nikolai Bukharin, Lenin; Alain Krivine, Elezioni o rivoluzione?; Alfonso Leonetti and Isaac Deutscher, Trockij e l'opposizione di sinistra; Crisi mondiale e soluzione socialista; The Truth about Trieste, (1942) (1944) (1964) (1968) (1968) (1969) (1969) (1979) (n.d.) (n.d.) (Box-folder 112: 2)
      - Leaflet, n.d. (Box-folder 112: 3)
  - Japan
    - Asian Youth Conference. Resolutions, 1974 (Box-folder 112: 4)
    - Citizens' Group to Convey Testimonies of Hiroshima and Nagasaki. Pamphlet. Give Me Water, (1972) (Box-folder 112: 5)
    - Communist League?Red Army Faction. Leaflet, 1969 (Box-folder 112: 6)
    - Japan Communist Youth
      - [ Akita Prefecture Monthly]. N.n., (n.d.) (Box-folder 112: 7)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1966 (Box-folder 112: 8)
    - Japan Revolutionary Communist League
      - [ Fourth International]
        - No. 6-15, (1967) (Box-folder 112: 9)
        - No. 5, (1968) (Box-folder 112: 10)
      - Fourth International
        - No. 1, no. 2-4, (1967) (1968) (Box-folder 112: 11)
        - No. 1, (1975) (Box-folder 112: 12)
      - [ Proletariat]. N.n., (1966) (Box-folder 112: 13)
      - Zenshin. No. 2, no. 3, no. 4, (1963) (1964) (1967) (Box-folder 112: 14)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 112: 15)
      - Leaflets and English translation of journal article, 1966-1979 (Box-folder 112: 16)
    - Japan Revolutionary Communist League?Revolutionary Marxist Faction
      - International Correspondence. No. 1, (1964) (Box-folder 112: 17)
      - Tsushin. No. 14, (1972) (Box-folder 112: 18)
      - Tsushin News Bulletin. No. 1, (1973) (Box-folder 112: 19)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 112: 20)
    - Okinawa Prefecture Council against Atomic and Hydrogen Bombs. Pamphlet. Okinawan White Paper (Box-folder 112: 21)
    - Revolutionary Left Movement. Japan Information. No. 1-3, (1967) (Box-folder 112: 22)
    - Sanrizuka International Solidarity Committee. Pamphlet. Narita Airport, Japan, Under Construction: The World's Most Dangerous Airport and the 12-Year People's Struggle against It, (1977) (Box-folder 112: 23)
    - Zengakuren. Pamphlet. Twenty Years' Struggle, (1967) (Box-folder 112: 24)
    - Unclassified by organization (Box 113)
      - [ Fourth International]. No. 100-102, no. 103-114, no. 117, 121-125, no. 127-135, 137, no. 140, 145, (1976) (1977) (1978) (1979) (1980) (Box-folder 113: 1)
      - [ New Criticism]. No. 1, (1968) (Box-folder 113: 2)
      - [ Soldiers and Workers]. No. 10, (1975) (Box-folder 113: 3)
      - Pamphlets
        - Topaz (Utah) War Relocation Center publication, ca. 1942-1945 (Box-folder 113: 4)
        - Ei Nagata, [ The Black Revolt]; Caroline Lund and Linda Jenness, [ Kate Millett's Sexual Politics and Norman Mailer's Prisoner of Sex], (1966) (1972) (Box-folder 113: 5)
        - Jacek Kuron and Karol Modzelewski, [ The Anti-Bureaucratic Revolution]; [ The Left Opposition: Memoirs of an Old Bolshevik]; [ The Vietnam Revolution and World Revolution], (1973) (1973) (n.d.) (Box-folder 113: 6)
      - Leaflet and printed articles, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 113: 7)
  - Luxembourg
    - Fonken. De fonken. No. 10-12, no. 15, no. 19-20, (1981) (1982) (1983) (Box-folder 113: 8)
    - Gruppe Revolutionärer Sozialisten. Klassenkampf. N.n., no. 1, (1979) (Box-folder 113: 9)
    - Ligue Communiste Révolutionnaire
      - Bolschewik. No. 1-2, (1972) (Box-folder 113: 10)
      - Bulletin intérieur / Internes Bulletin. No. 30-32, no. 33-45, (1972) (1973) (Box-folder 113: 11)
      - Kommunistische Texte aktuell. No. 1-2, 4, (1972) (Box-folder 113: 12)
      - Ró d Belval. No. 14, (1972) (Box-folder 113: 13)
      - Pamphlet. Ernest Mandel, Die Aktualität der leninistischen Organisationstheorie (Box-folder 113: 14)
    - Schülerfront. Rebell. No. 3, no. 6, 8, (1971) (1972) (Box-folder 113: 15)
  - Malaysia. Malaysian Socialists. Malaysian Socialist Review. No. 1-2, no. 3-4, (1976) (1977) (Box-folder 114: 1)
  - Mauritius
    - Groupement Révolutionnaire de l'ï¿½le Maurice. Mï¿½rice diboute! No. 1, no. 3, (1974) (1975) (Box-folder 114: 2)
    - Muvman Liberasyon Fam. Pamphlet. The Women's Liberation Movement in Mauritius, (1988) (Box-folder 114: 3)
  - Mexico
    - Alianza de Uniones y Sindicatos de Artes Graficas. Pamphlet. La justicía social en Mexico, (1945) (Box-folder 114: 4)
    - Circulo Hugo Blanco. Pamphlet. Michel Pablo, Qué es la Cuarta internacional?, (1964) (Box-folder 114: 5)
    - Comité Coordinador de Comités de Lucha. Boletín. No. 4, (1971) (Box-folder 114: 6)
    - Comité de Defensa de la Revolució n. Baluarte. No. 20, (1946) (Box-folder 114: 7)
    - Comité de Jovenes por el Socialismo. Jovenes por el socialismo. No. 1, no. 3, no. 5, (1976) (1977) (1978) (Box-folder 114: 8)
    - Comité Nacional de Lucha Obrera Ferroviaria. Pamphlet. El movimiento rielero, (1965) (Box-folder 114: 9)
    - Comité Obrero Revolucionario. Leaflet, 1970 (Box-folder 114: 10)
    - Comités Revolucionarios Obrero-Estudiantiles. Prensa revolucionaria. No. 2, (1969) (Box-folder 114: 11)
    - Confederació n de Trabajadores de México. Pamphlets. La C.T.M. y la carestia de la vida; Labor Condemns Trotskyism, (1937) (1938) (Box-folder 114: 12)
    - Confederació n Mexicana de Electricistas. Pamphlet. El "charrismo" sindical y la insurgencía de los ferroviarios, (1958) (Box-folder 114: 13)
    - Conferencía Interamericana de Agricultura. Pamphlet. Los revolucionarios ante Rusía y el stalinismo mundial, (1942) (Box-folder 114: 14)
    - Coordinadora Campesina Revolucionaria Independiente
      - El agrarista socialista. No. 3, (1977) (Box-folder 114: 15)
      - Pamphlet. La C.C.R.I. y la coordinadora nacional "Plan de Ayala" (Box-folder 114: 16)
      - Leaflet, 1978 (Box-folder 114: 17)
    - Council for Pan American Democracy. Pamphlet. Vicente Lombardo Toledano, Fifth Column in Mexico, (1941) (Box-folder 114: 18)
    - Frente Estudiantil Socialista
      - La chispa. No. 7, (n.d.) (Box-folder 114: 19)
      - Leaflets, 1966 (Box-folder 114: 20)
    - Grupo Comunista Internacionalista
      - Bandera roja suplemento. No. 1-4, 6-7, n.n., n.n., n.n., n.n., (1973) (1974) (1975) (n.d.) (Box-folder 114: 21)
      - Boletín de sociología de América latina. No. 2-3, (1974) (Box-folder 114: 22)
      - Boletín de sociología del siglo XX [title varies slightly]. N.n., no. 5, (1973) (Box-folder 114: 23)
      - Boletín interno
        - No. 1-3, (1969) (Box-folder 114: 24)
        - No. 4-7, 9, (1970) (Box-folder 114: 25)
        - No. 10, 12-13, n.n., (1971) (Box-folder 114: 26)
      - Boletín interno de discusió n. No. 1, (1974) (Box-folder 114: 27)
      - Brecha. No. 2-3, (1971) (Box-folder 114: 28)
      - Prefacio. No. 6, no. 7, (1973) (1974) (Box-folder 114: 29)
      - El profeta. No. 4, no. 5, (1973) (1974) (Box-folder 114: 30)
      - Tribuna roja. Vol. 1 no. 1, vol. 2 no. 3, (1973) (1974) (Box-folder 114: 31)
      - Internal circulated documents (Box 115)
        - 1970-1971 (Box-folder 115: 1)
        - 1972 (Box-folder 115: 2-3)
        - 1973-1975 (Box-folder 115: 4)
        - Undated (Box-folder 115: 5)
      - Pamphlet. Ernest Mandel, La teoría leninista de la organizació n, (1971) (Box-folder 115: 6)
      - Leaflets, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 115: 7)
    - Grupo Socialista Obrero
      - Boletín de informació n y discusió n. No. 2, (1945) (Box-folder 115: 8)
      - Tribuna socialista. No. 1, no. 2/3-12, 14, no. 16, 18, (1945) (1946) (1947) (Box-folder 115: 9)
    - Grupos Proletarios Revolucionarios. Topo obrero. No. 1, 1 [sic], 2-3, 7, (1974) (Box-folder 115: 10)
    - Juventud Marxista Revolucionaria
      - Boletín de discusió n. No. 1-10, (1973) (Box-folder 115: 11)
      - Virus rojo. No. 2, no. 3-19, 19 [sic], 20, 20 [sic], 21-22, no. 23-24, 24 [sic], 25-29, 31-33, (1971) (1972) (1973) (Box-folder 115: 12)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1973 (Box-folder 115: 13)
    - Juventud Socialista. Leaflet, n.d. (Box-folder 116: 1)
    - Liga Comunista. Mundo obrero. No. 8, no. 13-15, no. 18-19, (1940) (1941) (1942) (Box-folder 116: 2)
    - Liga Comunista Internacionalista [first]
      - Cuarta internacional. No. 24, (1939) (Box-folder 116: 3)
      - La nueva internacional. No. 2, 4, (1934) (Box-folder 116: 4)
      - Octubre. No. 1-2, (1935) (Box-folder 116: 5)
      - Pamphlets. Por la IV internacional; La guerra y la Cuarta internacional; Plataforma y estatutos, (1936) (1937) (1937) (Box-folder 116: 6)
      - Leaflet, 1938 (Box-folder 116: 7)
    - Liga Comunista Internacionalista [second]
      - Boletín de las ligas unidas [with Liga Socialista]. No. 1, (1976) (Box-folder 116: 8)
      - Internal circulated documents, 1976 (Box-folder 116: 9)
      - Pamphlets (all ). Capital monopolista de estado o estado del capital monopolista; China; La decadencia del bonapartismo mexicano; Plataforma; Por Campa contra JLP!; Pierre Salama, Introducció n a la economía marxista, 1976 (Box-folder 116: 10)
      - Leaflets, 1976 (Box-folder 116: 11)
    - Liga Obrera Marxista
      - Boletín de discusió n. N.n., (1964) (Box-folder 116: 12)
      - Boletín de informaciones. No. 9, (1967) (Box-folder 116: 13)
      - Boletín interno. No. 1, no. 4, (1964) (1966) (Box-folder 116: 14)
      - Frente obrero. No. 1-2, no. 3, (1976) (1977) (Box-folder 116: 15)
      - Lucha obrera. No. 1-2, (1954) (Box-folder 116: 16)
      - El obrero militante. No. 1, n.n., no. 4, 4 [sic], no. 6-8, no. 9-10, (1962) (1963) (1964) (1965) (Box-folder 116: 17)
      - Pamphlet. Carta abierta a Fidel Castro, (1966) (Box-folder 116: 18)
      - Leaflets, 1966 (Box-folder 116: 19)
    - Liga Obrera Revolucionaria. Boletín interno. No. 3, (1949) (Box-folder 116: 20)